https://www.enviropack.org.uk/privacy-policy/

We use cookies on this site to enhance your user experience. By clicking any link on this page you are giving your consent for us to set cookies. Privacy policyOk, I agree
Menu
ProductsCups & AccessoriesHot Food ContainersCold Food ContainersCatering PackagingDessert & CookiesTablewareSandwich & BreadBags & PouchesJanitorialSingle Wall cupsDouble Wall CupsRipple CupsLids for Hot cupsCold CupsLids for Cold cupsCups AccessoriesClear BottlesStrawsSugar Sticks
Paperboard ContainersSoup Containers & Noodle BoxesMicrowavable ContainersPaperboard Food BowlsBagasse ContainersTakeaway TraysAluminium Containers & LidsFoil Lined BagsHot Sandwich & Panini BagsSalt & Pepper SatchetsCarrier Bags & BoxesPizza BoxesBurger BoxesFish & ChipCurry & RicePastaTamper Proof ContainersOvenable Food Containers
Salad ContainersDeli & Portion PotsSushi BoxesPlattersSandwich and BaguetteSOS Bags & Carry Packs
Canape/AppetizerClamshellsServing CutleryServing BowlsSalad BoxesServing PlattersFood BoxesFood TraysFood BowlsFood PlatesDessert PotsCutlery
Ice Cream ContainersCakes BoxesDessert Pots & BoxesCookies & BiscuitsBaking Sheets
PlatesBowlsCutleryChopsticksSkewersNapkins
Paper & Film BagsSandwich Bags & BoxesBread & Baguette bagsWrapping/Deli & Greaseproof Sheets
Tin Tie bagsStand up Pouches / Doy PacksTuck Lid Window BoxesFlat Paper BagsFilm Fronted BagsOven-Able BagsTakeway / SOS Bags & Carry Packs
Blue Roll Cleaning ClothsPPE
Cups & AccessoriesSingle Wall cupsDouble Wall CupsRipple CupsLids for Hot cupsCold CupsLids for Cold cupsCups AccessoriesClear BottlesStrawsSugar Sticks
Hot Food ContainersPaperboard ContainersSoup Containers & Noodle BoxesMicrowavable ContainersPaperboard Food BowlsBagasse ContainersTakeaway TraysAluminium Containers & LidsFoil Lined BagsHot Sandwich & Panini BagsSalt & Pepper SatchetsCarrier Bags & BoxesPizza BoxesBurger BoxesFish & ChipCurry & RicePastaTamper Proof ContainersOvenable Food Containers
Cold Food ContainersSalad ContainersDeli & Portion PotsSushi BoxesPlattersSandwich and BaguetteSOS Bags & Carry Packs
Catering PackagingCanape/AppetizerClamshellsServing CutleryServing BowlsSalad BoxesServing PlattersFood BoxesFood TraysFood BowlsFood PlatesDessert PotsCutlery
Dessert & CookiesIce Cream ContainersCakes BoxesDessert Pots & BoxesCookies & BiscuitsBaking Sheets
TablewarePlatesBowlsCutleryChopsticksSkewersNapkins
Sandwich & BreadPaper & Film BagsSandwich Bags & BoxesBread & Baguette bagsWrapping/Deli & Greaseproof Sheets
Bags & PouchesTin Tie bagsStand up Pouches / Doy PacksTuck Lid Window BoxesFlat Paper BagsFilm Fronted BagsOven-Able BagsTakeway / SOS Bags & Carry Packs
JanitorialBlue Roll Cleaning ClothsPPE
Compostable ProductsCups & AccessoriesHot Food ContainersCold Food ContainersCatering PackagingDessert & CookiesTablewareSandwich & BreadBags & PouchesJanitorialCompostable Paper Cups & LidsCompostable Cold Cups & LidsEco AccessoriesCompostable Straws
Compostable Paperboard ContainersCompostable Soup Containers & LidsCompostable TraysBagasse ContainersCompostable BowlsEco Hot Sandwich BagsEco Carrier Bags & BoxesPizza Boxes
Compostable Salad ContainersCompostable PlattersSOS BagsCompostable Deli & Portion Pots
Compostable ClamshellsCompostable Serving BowlsCompostable Salad BoxesCompostable Serving PlattersCompostable Food BoxesCompostable Food TraysCompostable Food BowlsCompostable PlatesEco Cutlery
Compostable Ice Cream ContainersCompostable Dessert Pots and Boxes
Sugarbagasse BowlsSugarbagasse PlatesPalm Leaf BowlsPalm Leaf PlatesCompostable Cutlery
Compostable Bread BagsCompostable Baguette Bags & BoxesCompostable Sandwich Bags & BoxesCompostable Film Fronted Bags
Eco Flat Paper BagsCompostable Film Fronted BagsCompostable Tin Tie Bags With WindowCompostable Stand up PouchesPaper Carrier Bags
Blue Roll Cleaning Cloths
Cups & AccessoriesCompostable Paper Cups & LidsCompostable Cold Cups & LidsEco AccessoriesCompostable Straws
Hot Food ContainersCompostable Paperboard ContainersCompostable Soup Containers & LidsCompostable TraysBagasse ContainersCompostable BowlsEco Hot Sandwich BagsEco Carrier Bags & BoxesPizza Boxes
Cold Food ContainersCompostable Salad ContainersCompostable PlattersSOS BagsCompostable Deli & Portion Pots
Catering PackagingCompostable ClamshellsCompostable Serving BowlsCompostable Salad BoxesCompostable Serving PlattersCompostable Food BoxesCompostable Food TraysCompostable Food BowlsCompostable PlatesEco Cutlery
Dessert & CookiesCompostable Ice Cream ContainersCompostable Dessert Pots and Boxes
TablewareSugarbagasse BowlsSugarbagasse PlatesPalm Leaf BowlsPalm Leaf PlatesCompostable Cutlery
Sandwich & BreadCompostable Bread BagsCompostable Baguette Bags & BoxesCompostable Sandwich Bags & BoxesCompostable Film Fronted Bags
Bags & PouchesEco Flat Paper BagsCompostable Film Fronted BagsCompostable Tin Tie Bags With WindowCompostable Stand up PouchesPaper Carrier Bags
JanitorialBlue Roll Cleaning Cloths
Bespoke & BrandingPrinted Clear Cold CupsPrinted NapkinsPrinted Double Wall Paper CupsPrinted Paperboard ContainersPrinted Pouches and Tin Tie bagsPrinted Deli and Portion PotsPrinted Tuck Lid BoxesPrinted Ripple CupsPrinted Soup & Ice Cream ContainersPrinted Pizza BoxesPrinted LabelsPrinted Single Wall Paper CupsPrinted Compostable Paper CupsPrinted Paper Take-away BagsPrinted Sleeves for cupsPrinted Clear Cold CupsPrinted Deli and Portion PotsPrinted LabelsPrinted NapkinsPrinted Tuck Lid BoxesPrinted Single Wall Paper CupsPrinted Double Wall Paper CupsPrinted Ripple CupsPrinted Compostable Paper CupsPrinted Paperboard ContainersPrinted Soup & Ice Cream ContainersPrinted Paper Take-away BagsPrinted Pouches and Tin Tie bagsPrinted Pizza BoxesPrinted Sleeves for cupsSustainabilityNew ArrivalsGet Samples
Account
Free UK mainland delivery on orders above £99 (excluding VAT) | Eco-Friendly & Sustainable food packaging specialist since 2002
Home
Privacy policy
Privacy policy
Cups & Accessories
Single Wall cups
Double Wall Cups
Ripple Cups
Lids for Hot cups
Janitorial
XDear Customer,We are currently experiencing minor delays in dispatching some orders, due to the high volume of parcels being processed through our couriers’ networks. Orders are being dispatched on a daily basis however there may be an additional delay of 1-2 days in delivering your order.
Please accept our apologies for any inconvenience caused and be assured that we are monitoring the situation closely. We would advise checking our website regularly for updates as the situation progresses and hopefully improves.
Do not hesitate to contact our sales team at sales@enviropack.org.uk if you have any queries.
Important: Christmas & New Year delivery schedule
Please note our last order dates for Pre-Christmas Delivery for:
Pallet orders: Friday 18st December 2020, before 1pm. Pallet orders placed after 1pm on the Friday 18th December will be delivered during the week commencing 4th January 2021.
Courier orders: Tuesday 22nd December 2020, before 1pm. Orders placed after 1pm on Tuesday 22nd December and 28th will be dispatched on Tuesday 29th December 2020. Orders placed after the 29th December will be dispatched during the week commencing 4th January 2021.
Kind regards,The Enviropack Team
Enviropack Ltd knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Enviropack Ltd , you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
What Personal Information About Customers Does Enviropack Ltd Gather? The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Enviropack Ltd . Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store features, and communication with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our website.
E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "Subscription" preferences by logging into your account.
What About Cookies? Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
Does Enviropack Ltd Share the Information It Receives? We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.
How Secure Is Information About Me? We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our products or services. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer by clicking the "log off" link located in the side menu.
Which Information Can I Access? Enviropack Ltd gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions If you choose to visit Enviropack Ltd, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of our local state. If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the "Contact Us" link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
Information You Give Us You provide most such information when you search, buy, order, post reviews, or other methods of communication via our website or email to Enviropack Ltd . As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and credit card information.
Automatic Information For security purposes Enviropack Ltd sometimes collects and analyses the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for your protection for tracking purposes in the unfortunate event that someone gains access to your personal or financial information and opens an account, or makes purchases under your name.
Questions Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff using our contact page.
